Office of the Vice-President, Research fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Committees, 1977 - 2000; F-86-5; 1.16 m of textual records
  - SFU Committees, 1977 - 2000; F-86-5-1; 75 cm of textual records
    - President's Research Grant Committee, 1977 - 1983; F-86-5-1-10; 13 cm of textual records
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, 1981; F-86-5-1-10-2 (Archival box - standard 86-38)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1982; F-86-5-1-10-3 (Archival box - standard 86-38)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1982; F-86-5-1-10-4 (Archival box - standard 86-38)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1983; F-86-5-1-10-5 (Archival box - standard 86-39)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1983; F-86-5-1-10-6 (Archival box - standard 86-39)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 3, 1983; F-86-5-1-10-7 (Archival box - standard 86-39)
    - Burnaby Lands Committee, 1995 - 1997; F-86-5-1-11; 5 cm of textual records
      Burnaby Lands Committee
      - Burnaby Lands Committee, vol. 1, 1995 - 1997; F-86-5-1-11-1 (Archival box - standard 86-39)
        Restricted in part
      - Burnaby Lands Committee, vol. 2, 1995 - 1997; F-86-5-1-11-2 (Archival box - standard 86-39)
  - Non-SFU Committees, 1985 - 1999; F-86-5-2; 41 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the participation of the Vice-President, Research on non-university committees as a representative for Simon Fraser University.
    - Science Council of British Columbia, 1988 - 1990; F-86-5-2-1; 2 cm of textual records
      Science Council of B.C.
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, 1988 - 1990; F-86-5-2-1-1 (Archival box - standard 86-40)
    - NSERC Allocations Sub-Committee, 1993 - 1996; F-86-5-2-2; 3 cm of textual records
      NSERC Allocations Sub-Committee
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1993 - 1996; F-86-5-2-2-1 (Archival box - standard 86-40)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1993 - 1996; F-86-5-2-2-2 (Archival box - standard 86-40)
    - Royal Society of Canada: Committee on University Research, 1989 - 1991; F-86-5-2-3; 2 cm of textual records
      Royal Society of Canada - Committee on University Research
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, 1989 - 1991; F-86-5-2-3-1 (Archival box - standard 86-40)
    - B.C. Science Council: Sparks Steering Committee, 1989 - 1990; F-86-5-2-4; 2 cm of textual records
      B.C. Science Council - Sparks Steering Committee
      - Correspondence and newsletters, 1989 - 1990; F-86-5-2-4-1 (Archival box - standard 86-40)
    - B.C. University Committee on Sustainable Development, 1991 - 1994; F-86-5-2-5; 2 cm of textual records
      B.C. University Committee on Sustainable Development
      - Correspondence and working papers, 1991 - 1994; F-86-5-2-5-1 (Archival box - standard 86-40)
    - Celebration Science 2000: Local Steering Committee, 1996 - 1997; F-86-5-2-6; 2 cm of textual records
      Celebration Science 2000 - Local Steering Committee
      - Correspondence and minutes, 1996 - 1997; F-86-5-2-6-1 (Archival box - standard 86-40)
    - Canadian Research Management Association, 1998; F-86-5-2-7; 2 cm of textual records
      Canadian Research Management Association
      - Working papers, 1998; F-86-5-2-7-1 (Archival box - standard 86-40)
    - SSHRC Strategic Panel, 1990 - 1993; F-86-5-2-8; 2 cm of textual records
      SSHRC Strategic Panel
      - Correspondence and reports, 1990 - 1993; F-86-5-2-8-1 (Archival box - standard 86-41)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on B.C. Innovation Collaboration, 1998; F-86-5-2-9; 2 cm of textual records
      Ad Hoc Committee on B.C. Innovation Collaboration
      - Correspondence and working papers, 1998; F-86-5-2-9-1 (Archival box - standard 86-41)
    - C.F.I. Steering Committee, 1998 - 1999; F-86-5-2-10; 2 cm of textual records
      C.F.I. Steering Committee
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, 1998 - 1999; F-86-5-2-10-1 (Archival box - standard 86-41)
    - Association of Universities and Colleges of Canada (AUCC), 1992 - 1998; F-86-5-2-11; 11 cm of textual records
      Association of Universities and Colleges of Canada
      - National Vice Presidents research meetings, 1992 - 1997; F-86-5-2-11-1 (Archival box - standard 86-41)
      - AUCC/CARL Task Force on Academic Libraries Subcommittee on Intellectual Property, 1995 - 1996; F-86-5-2-11-2 (Archival box - standard 86-41)
      - AUCC Cancopy Negotiating Committee, vol. 1, 1995 - 1997; F-86-5-2-11-3 (Archival box - standard 86-41)
      - AUCC Cancopy Negotiating Committee, vol. 2, 1995 - 1997; F-86-5-2-11-4 (Archival box - standard 86-41)
      - AUCC Cancopy Negotiating Committee, vol. 3, 1995 - 1997; F-86-5-2-11-5 (Archival box - standard 86-42)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, 1996 - 1998; F-86-5-2-11-6 (Archival box - standard 86-42)
    - Canadian Association of University Research Administrators (CAURA), 1985 - 1999; F-86-5-2-12; 11 cm of textual records
      Canadian Association of University Research Administrators
      - CAURA meetings, vol. 1, 1985 - 1989; F-86-5-2-12-1 (Archival box - standard 86-42)
      - CAURA meetings, vol. 2, 1985 - 1989; F-86-5-2-12-2 (Archival box - standard 86-42)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, 1996; F-86-5-2-12-3 (Archival box - standard 86-42)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1997 - 1998; F-86-5-2-12-4 (Archival box - standard 86-42)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1997 - 1998; F-86-5-2-12-5 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
      - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 3, 1997 - 1998; F-86-5-2-12-6 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
      - CAURA Executive, 1998 - 1999; F-86-5-2-12-7 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
      - Correspondence, 1999; F-86-5-2-12-8 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
- Publications, 1985 - 2006; F-86-6; 11 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications produced by the Office of the Vice-President, Research. Records include a directory of SFU research institutes and centres, promotional books on SFU's research accomplishments, circulars, grant writing workshop posters, and bi-monthly newsletters reporting on research updates.
  The publications found in this series were acquired by the Archives from a variety of sources. Although the accessions from the Office of the Vice-President, Research contained a number of departmental publications, most of the publications were collected by Archives staff as part of an artificial university-wide periodicals collection and then processed as part of the fonds.
  - SFU Directory of Research Institutes and Centres, 1985; F-86-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - SFU Research, 1988; F-86-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - SFU Environmental Iniatives Report, 1990; F-86-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - "Research Links" newsletter, 1992 - 1998; F-86-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - Research at SFU, 1995; F-86-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - Research Handbook, 1995 - 1996; F-86-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - Research Partners circular, 1995 - 1998; F-86-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - SFU Research Matters (vol. 1), 1997; F-86-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - Grant writing/management workshop poster, 1998; F-86-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - SFU Research Matters (vol. 2), 1998; F-86-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - Highlighting Research at SFU, 2000; F-86-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - "Research Links" newsletter, 2000 - 2005; F-86-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - SFU Research, 2001; F-86-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - "ORE News" Office of Research Ethics newsletter, 2003 - 2006; F-86-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 86-43)
  - SFU Research Matters circular, 2006; F-86-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 86-43)